A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, General Files (Room 5600), 2001-2006, RG 55 FA1254
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Education, 2001-2006; 6
  - Education - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 5-8)
    Includes: African Children's Fund; Aspen Institute; Atlantic Corridor USA, Inc.; Blanton-Peale Institute; Cato Policy Report; Center for Arts Education; Center for Functional Research; Center for Public Interest Research; Center for a Sustainable Future; Collaborative for Academic, Social, and Emotional Learning (CASEL); Foundation for Our Future; Foundation for Responsible Energy Education; Friends of Wood Island Lighthouse; Gilder Lehrman Institute of American History; Hudson Link for Higher Education in Prison; Indigenous Language Institute; Inner-City Scholarship Fund; Institute of International Education; National Humanities Center; National Mentoring Partnership; Ndakinna Education Center; New Dimensions Foundations; Pocantico Hills School Foundation; ProEnglish; Room to Read; Roosevelt Institute; Witness.
  - Character Education Partnership, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Classroom, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Coalition on Urban Renewal and Education, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Foundation for Shamanic Studies, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Greenacre Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Haas Center, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    John Gardner Public Service Fellowship, in memory of John Gardner.
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - International Consciousness Research Laboratories, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National Geographic Society, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Outdoor Leadership School, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - New Visions for Public Schools, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Ojai Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - A-G, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 10-13)
  - Colleges - H-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 1-8)
  - Colleges - Berry College, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - Brown University, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Colleges - Cambridge College, Elizabeth J. McCormack Chair in Humanities, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Colleges - California Institute of Integral Studies, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - College of the Atlantic, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Columbia University, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Columbia - (National) Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse (CASA), 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Columbia - Center for Complimentary and Alternative Medicine, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Cornell University, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - Dartmouth College, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Includes: Nelson A. Rockefeller Center at Dartmouth College.
  - Colleges - Duke University, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Includes: Graduate School of Education; Harvard Law School Fund; President and Fellows of Harvard College, Harvard Medical School.
  - Colleges - Harvard University - Center for Health and the Global Environment, 2001-2006 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - Gardner, Howard, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Manhattanville College, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Marlboro College, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - MIT - Meetings of the Corporation, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - MIT - Reports of the Committees on the Status of Women Faculty, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Colleges - New York University, 2001-2006 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Includes: Courant Institute; Morawetz, Cathleen.
  - Colleges - Princeton University - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 1-7)
    Includes: Admission Office; Alumni Publication; Appiah, Kwame Anthony; Class of 1940; Class of 1962; Contributions; Department of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering; Director of Development; Eisgruber, Christopher; Engineering Anomalies Research (Princeton Engineering Anomalies Research (PEAR); Football; Gifts to Princeton; Guttman, Amy; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions (Department of Politics); Office of Development Communications; Office of the President; Office of the Provost; Office of the Recording Secretary; Office of the Vice President and Secretary; Old Guard Reunion; Princeton Blairstown Center; Princeton Theological Seminary; Princeton Weekly Bulletin; Revised Trustee Pocket Calendars; Shapiro, Harold and Vivian; Tang Center; 257th Commencement; Vice President for Development; Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs.
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Annual Giving, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Board of Trustees, 2001-2006 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Center for the Study of Religion, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Class of 1932, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - President's Room, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - School of Engineering and Applied Science, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - University Center for Human Values, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - Princeton University - Thomas H. Wright Scholarship Fund, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Includes: Harper Society.
  - Colleges - University of Kansas, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Colleges - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, 2001-2006 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Includes: Department of Geosciences.
  - Colleges - University of Pittsburgh Cancer Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Colleges - University of Texas at Austin, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Colleges - University of Vermont, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Includes: School of Natural Resources, Recreation Management Program; Vermont Cancer Center.
  - Colleges - University of Virginia, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Includes: Health System; Miller Center of Public Affairs.
  - Colleges - Vermont Law School, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Colleges - West Virginia University, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Includes; Rockefeller Neurosciences Institute.
  - Colleges - Yale University, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Includes: J. Richardson Dilworth Professorship Fund.
  - Foundations - A-F, 2001-2006 (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
  - Foundations - G-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
  - Foundations - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Foundations - Foundation for a Conference on Faith and Order in North America, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Foundations - Halo Foundation, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Foundations - Hawaii Community Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Foundations - Aldo Leopold Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Foundations - Manitou Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Foundations - George C. Marshall Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Foundations - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Foundations - Hideo Sasaki Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Historical Societies - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Historical Societies - New-York Historical Society, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Historical Societies - Woodstock Historical Society, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Housing - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Includes International House - New York; West End Revitalization Association.
  - Radio and TV - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
    Includes: E TV Endowment of South Carolina; KUT 90.5 FM; National Public Radio; New Dimensions World Broadcasting Network; PRI - Public Radio International; Public Affairs Television; Wisdom Media Group; WNYC.
  - Radio and TV - KCTS, The Public Radio Network, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Radio and TV - KLRN - TV, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Radio and TV - KUED 7 Public Television, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Radio and TV - WETA, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Radio and TV - WNET Channel 13, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Schools - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 2-5)
    Includes: Bank Street College of Education; Buckley School; ChiIdren's Storefront; Churchill School and Center; Episcopal Divinity School; Haystack Mountain School of Crafts; High School for Environmental Studies; Ho'ala School; Jackson Hole Christian Academy; Madeira School; Manhattan Country School; Manhattan East School for Arts and Academics; Miss Porter's School; New Vision for Public School; Outward Bound USA; Pocantico Hills Central School; Pocantico Hills School Foundation; Punahou School; Alexander Robertson School; Ross School; St. Bernard's School (Not in file - note by SVP, Family Office, December 12, 2007); St. Mary's School; St. Paul's School; Sidwell Friends School; Teton Sciences School, Kelly, WY; Stony Brook School; Washington County Schools; Woodstock School Fund.
  - Schools - Brearley School, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Schools - Hackley School, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Schools - Mill Neck Manor School for the Deaf, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Schools - St. John School of the Arts, 2001-2006 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Schools - Trevor Day School, 2001-2006 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Schools - Trinity School, 2001-2006 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- H, 2001-2006; 7
  - Historic Hudson Valley - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
  - Horticulture - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
    Includes: Belt Collins Hawaii, Ltd.; Garden Club of America; Hudson and Pacific Designs, Inc.; Landscape Architecture Foundation; National Tropical Botanical Garden; Resortscapes, Inc.; Sasaki Associates, Inc. Wirth Design Associates.
  - Horticulture - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Horticulture - New York Botanical Garden, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
  - Horticulture - Old Westbury Gardens, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- International Relations, 2001-2006; 8
  - International Relations - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Includes: American Friends of Versailles; Children's Institute International; Friends of Africa Foundation; Global Security Institute; Near East Foundation; Queen Sofia Spanish Institute; World Affairs Council.
  - Argentina - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Includes: Argentine-American Society of New York.
  - Asia - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Includes: Asian Cultural Council; Asia Society; Cambodia's Cardamom Mountains.
  - China - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Includes: China Institute; China Institute in America; Culture and Civilization of China.
  - France - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Includes: French-American Foundation.
  - France - International Rescue Committee, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Kenya - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Includes: Gallmann Memorial Foundation.
  - Foreign Aid - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Includes: Trickle Up Program.
  - Foreign Aid - Synergos Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Includes: Council on Foreign Relations; Foreign Policy Association.
  - Peace - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Includes: Center for Sustainable Peace and Development; International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War.
  - United Nations - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Includes: United Nations Day in Virginia Commission; United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (USA Committee for UNESCO); World Federation of United Nations Associations.
  - United Nations - United Nations Association of the USA, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - United States Government - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies.
- Medicine, 2001-2006; 9
  - Medicine - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 38, Folder 1-10)
    Includes: Alzheimer's Association; American Association on Mental Retardation; American Foundation for AIDS Research (AMFAR); American Heart Association; American-Italian Cancer Foundation (AICF); Anomalous Phenomena Research Center; Arcus Group; Asthma Van Initiative; Bedscapes International; Bone Marrow Foundation; Breastcancer.org; Campaign for Forgiveness Research; Cancer Hope Network; Cancer Research Institute; Donna M. Crandall Memorial Foundation; Fracture Service Fund, Inc.; Friends of Norris Cotton Cancer Center; G & P Foundation for Cancer Research; Gilda's Club of Westchester; House Ear Institute; Institute for Healing in Society and Medicine; Jackson Laboratory; Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International; Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation; Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation; Thomas G. Labrecque Classic; Albert and Mary Lasker Foundation; Lerner Medical Technology; Lupus Research Institute; National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction; National Hemophilia Foundation; National Kidney Foundation of Central New York, Inc.; National Parkinson's Foundation; New England School of Acupuncture; New York Blood Center; New York Organ Donor Network; NY Open Center; Novartis International; Open Door Family Medical Center; Open Eye Pictures; Parkinson's Disease Foundation; Pasteur Foundation; Pier Paolo Pandolfi, de Rinaldis, M.D., PhD.; Damon Runyon Cancer Research Fund; Smile Train; Spinal Research Foundation; Spirituality and Well Being; Stony Brook Pediatrics Endowment for Children; Lauri Strauss Leukemia Foundation; Traditional Acupuncture Institute, Inc.; Dr. J. Craig Venter; Wisdom Television and Radio.
  - Alliance for Lupus Research, 2001-2006 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Alternative Therapies in Health and Medicine, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - American Cancer Society, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Arthritis Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Basic Research Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Breast Cancer Research Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Center for Mind-Body Medicine, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Commonweal, 2001-2006 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
  - The Continuum Center for Health and Healing (Beth Israel Medical Center), 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Freedom Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Health Choices, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Health, LLC, 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Health Medicine Forum, 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Cancer Prevention, 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - International Longevity Center, 2001-2006 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
  - International Longevity Center - Dr. Robert N. Butler, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - International Medical Corps, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Juvenile Diabetes Research Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Institute for Cancer Research, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Marijuana Policy Project, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Marshfield Clinic, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Mind-Body Medical Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Mind Brain Body and Health Initiative, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 8-9)
  - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - National Marfan Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - National Organization of Circumcision Information Resource Center, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - New York Physicians Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Omega Institute for Holistic Studies, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Paget Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Preventive Medicine Research Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Pulmonary Fibrosis Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - RENEW, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Samueli Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Tai Sophia Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Uniformed Services University of the Health Sciences, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - VZW Research Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - Webb - Waring Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholism - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 2-5)
    Includes: Beth Israel Medical Center; Cape Cod Hospital; Children's Hospital at Montefiore; Children's Hospital Trust; Eisenhower Medical Center (Betty Ford Center); James A. Haley Veterans Hospital; Helen Hayes Hospital; Huron Hospital; Jewish Hospital Foundation; Maine Medical Center Family Practice Center; Montefiore Medical Center; Mount Ascutney Hospital; Mount Sinai School of Medicine; New York Hospital Cornell Medical Center, Center for Special Studies; New York Weill Cornell Medical Center; New York Medical College; New York - Presbyterian Hospital, Fund for Medicine; North Hawaii Community Hospital; Alice Peck Day Memorial Hospital; Barbara Sinatra Children's Center (at Eisenhower); St. John's Medical Center Foundation; St. Patrick Hospital; Zena and Michael A. Weiner Cardiovascular Institute; Westchester Medical Center.
  - Hospitals - Calvary Hospital, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Hospital for Special Surgery, 2001-2006 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Massachusetts General Hospital, Boston, 2001-2006 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 45, Folder 2-7)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Overseers and Managers, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Integrative Medicine, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Paul Marks Prize for Cancer Research and for Excellence, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Media Reports, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Memorial Service for Dr. William Fair, 2002 March 29 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Office of the President, 2001-2006 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Printed Matter, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals - New York Weill Cornell Medical Center, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Hospitals - St. John's Hospital, Jackson, WY, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Hospitals - United Hospital Fund, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Includes: American Association on Mental Retardation; Washington County Mental Health Services, Inc.
  - Narcotics - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Includes: Phoenix House.
  - Narcotics - Drug Policy Alliance, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Narcotics - Lindesmith Center, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Philanthropy, 2001-2006; 10
  - Philanthropy - A-Z (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Foundation Center, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Linkages in Philanthropy, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Philanthropic Collaborative, 2001-2006 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Philanthropy Advisors, 2001-2004 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Politics, 2001-2006; 11
  - Politics - A-N, 2001-2006 (Box 49, Folder 3-5)
    Includes: Bush-Cheny '04; Larry Craig; Dean for America; Democracy for America; Joe Driscoll; Eristoff for State Senate; Jim Farrin for Congress; John Faso; Friends of Pataki; Help America's Leaders (HAL PAC); Gail Hilson; Richard Holbrooke; Amo Houghton; Sue Kelly for Congress; Leahy for U.S. Senator; Metropolitan Republican Club; Robert Morganthau; Naples for Congress; New York Republican County Committee; New York State Conservative Party.
  - Politics - O-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
    Includes: George Pataki; Presidential Gala 2001; Presidential Inaugural Committee; Presidential Roundtable; Republican National Committee; Republican Party of Florida; Republican Pro-Choice Coalition; Bill Richardson for Governor; Tom Ridge; Senator Jay Rockefeller; Win Rockefeller Reception (2001 June 13); Richard Romero; Vermont Democratic House Campaign Inc.; Vermont Democratic Party; Vermont Senate Victory; Wellstone for Senate.
  - Republican Main Street Partnership, 2001-2006 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Population, 2001-2006; 12
  - Population - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Includes: International Planned Parenthood Federation; Plan USA; Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc.; Population Connection; Population Council.
  - Population Action International, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Population Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Abortion - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Includes National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League of New York State (NARAL-NY).
- R-W, 2001-2006; 13
  - Race Relations - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Includes: New York Urban League.
  - Real Estate - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Includes: British Virgin Islands; Brown Harris Stevens; Caneel Bay Resort; Enterprise Foundation; Grand Teton Lodge Company; Hyatt-Dorado; Mauna Kea Beach Hotel; Pocantico Hills Village Green; Rockefeller Center; Stribling Private Brokerage.
  - Recreation - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Includes: 3 Creek Ranch; Arthur Ashe Institute for Urban Health; Croquet; Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Club; Polo Training Foundation.
  - Recreation - Union Arena, Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - A-Z, 2001-2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller and Company, Inc. - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    Primarily Venrock Associates.
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 56, Folder 1-2, Box 57, Folder 1)
    Includes: Conference Center - Pocantico; Bill Moody; Patriot's Energy Pledge; Pocantico Forum.
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Healing Energy Conference, 2001-2006 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Includes: Virginia DiFronzo; Farm Family Insurance Company; Ruth T. Kuhlmann; Ann Mortimer; Josie Reyes; Rockefeller Risk Advisors (Division of Marsh Private Client Services); Amber Sprandlin; Granville W. Waterman.
  - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z, 2001-2002 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Includes: Annual Report, 2000 and 2001.
  - Westchester Organizations - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Includes Hilltop Engine Company No. 1.
  - Winrock International - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Center for Development Policy, 2001-2006 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Religion, 2001-2006; 14
  - Religion - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)